Finding Aid for the Eiko Ishioka papers LSC.2288
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 9: Advertising, 1962-2005
  - Subseries 9.13: Parco: Kenji Sawada campaigns, 1979-1980
    - Slides, transparencies, negatives, photographs (binders and file boxes), circa 1979-1980 (Box 366, Box 367, Box 368, Box 369, Box 370, Box 371, Box 372)
    - The Day Has Come to Speak about Men: poster, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Who Will Make the Pulse of Our Time Beat Faster?: poster, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Who Will Ring the Heart of this Era.: poster, 1979 (Box 23)
    - Kenji Sawada (oversize horizontal, two versions): posters, 1979 (Box 303)
  - Subseries 9.14: Parco: other campaigns, 1971-1983
    Posters and related material for numerous other Parco campaigns. See also Series 11 for film and other audiovisual material relating to Parco television commercials.
    - 12.12.Open: photographs, circa 1976 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - 12.12.Open: poster, circa 1976 (Box 25)
    - All That Jyoji!: photographs, circa 1980 (Box 163, Folder 1, Box 715, Folder 24)
    - All That Jyoji!: slides and transparencies, circa 1980 (Box 378, Box 379)
    - All That Jyoji!/ Kichijyoji Opens September 21: posters, 1980 (Box 302)
      Posters are oversize, horizontal.
    - All That Jyoji!: poster production material, undated (Box 308)
    - Anti-Sentimentalism: poster (version 1), 1974 (Box 21)
    - Anti-Sentimentalism: poster (version 2), 1974 (Box 26)
    - Be Natural. Go Nature.: poster, 1971 (Box 25)
    - Dominique Sanda: slides, transparencies, negatives, circa 1978 (Box 372, Box 373)
    - Dominique Sanda: posters, 1978 (Box 25)
    - Dominique Sanda: posters (oversize horizontal), 1978 (Box 303)
    - Don't Stare at the Nude; Be Naked: photographs (Aurore Clement), circa 1975 (Box 162, Folder 9)
    - Don't Stare at the Nude; Be Naked: poster (version 1, Aurore Clement), 1975 (Box 19)
    - Don't Stare at the Nude; Be Naked: poster (version 2), 1975 (Box 26)
    - Dressed to Kill and No Place to Go: color transparencies, circa 1980 (Box 429)
    - Dressed to Kill and No Place to Go: snapshots, circa 1980 (Box 715, Folder 23)
    - Dressed to Kill and No Place to Go: posters, 1980 (Box 20)
    - Dressed To Kill and No Place to Go: poster production material, undated (Box 51, Box 308)
    - Fashion Is More than Just Imitation: slides, circa 1975 (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - Fashion Is More than Just Imitation: poster (Rene Russo), 1975 (Box 27)
    - Girls Be Ambitious!: photographs, circa 1975 (Box 162, Folder 8, Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Girls Be Ambitious!: slides, circa 1975 (Box 376, Box 377)
    - Girls Be Ambitious!: posters, 1975 (Box 22)
    - Goodbye My Hometown, Fashion Has No Borders.: poster, 1974 (Box 26)
    - Kimiko: poster, 1976 (Box 19)
    - Life Is Short, the Night Is Longer: photographs, circa 1976 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Life is Short, the Night is Longer: slides, circa 1976 (Box 380)
    - Life Is Short, The Night Is Longer: poster, 1976 (Box 22)
    - Men! Let's Become More Beautiful for Women!: poster (version 1), 1976 (Box 22)
    - Men Let's Be More Beautiful for Women: poster (version 2), circa 1977 (Box 25)
    - A Model Is More than Just a Pretty Face: photographs (snapshots), circa 1975 (Box 162, Folder 10)
    - A Model Is More than Just a Pretty Face: slides, circa 1975 (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - A Model Is More than Just a Pretty Face: poster (Rene Russo), 1975 (Box 27)
    - The Nightingale Sings for No One but Herself: slides, circa 1976 (Box 358, Folder 4-6, Box 374, Box 375)
    - The Nightingale Sings for No One but Herself: posters, 1976 (Box 18)
      Series of seven individual posters with models June Murphy, Grace Jones, Barbara Jackson, Barbara Summers, Denis Pascal, Jan Maden, and Dorris Smith.
    - Of People Who Are Sensitive to Live: poster, 1972 (Box 25)
    - Osaka Play Map: poster, undated (Box 597)
    - Our Summer: poster, undated (Box 26)
    - Parco Part 2: poster, undated (Box 22)
    - Parco's Goodbye to the Ocean: poster, undated (Box 26)
    - Sense of Parco.: poster, 1972 (Box 26)
    - Sense of Parco Is Inherited, or Not.: poster, 1974 (Box 27)
    - Shibuya Men Are Gazing at Tomorrow.: poster, undated (Box 26)
    - Shibuya Women are Burning with Tomorrow.: poster, 1973 (Box 26)
    - Shinsaibashi Opening December 12th!: poster, 1971 (Box 25)
    - Summer in Parco: poster, undated (Box 22)
    - Summer of Parco's Color - Azule: poster, circa 1975 (Box 26)
    - Summer of Parco's Color - Brown: poster, 1975 (Box 26)
    - There Are No Rails on the High Heel Express: poster, 1977 (Box 19)
    - Very Parco series: posters, 1983 (Box 23, Box 24)
      Posters include The Kimono, The Book, The Dress, The Shoes, The Music, The Sports, The Restaurant, The Theater.
    - The Wind of Parco in the Eyes. December 1st the Birth of Chibaginza: posters, 1976 (Box 26)
    - A Woman Can Feel a Foreign Country: posters, 1975 (Box 20)
    - You Are Fantastic! How Old Are You?: poster, 1973 (Box 21)
    - Smaller posters (Box 27)
    - Various campaigns: photographs and contact sheets, circa 1974-1978 (Box 163, Folder 4-7, Box 193, Folder 4-9)
    - Various campaigns: slides, transparencies, negatives, photographs, circa 1970s, 2009 (Box 163, Folder 8, Box 381, Box 382, Box 383, Box 384, Box 385, Box 386, Box 387, Box 388, Box 389, Box 390, Box 391, Box 392, Box 397, Box 424, Box 431, Box 708)
    - Various campaigns: production material, circa 1976-1977, 1983, circa 1983 (Box 347, Box 348, Folder 1-2, Box 351, Folder 2-4, Box 352, Folder 8, Box 481, Folder 3)
      Includes sketches, typeface, dummies, print ads, layouts, photographs, logotype.
    - Various campaigns: poster production material, undated (Box 49, Box 53)
    - Various campaigns: publicity and publications, 1976-2005 (Box 519, Folder 1-2)
      Various magazines and publications including Across (1977-1978) containing Parco spreads for Kenya, Morocco, and Dominique Sanda campaigns; and Parco Report (1976-1977).
    - Portfolio: slides, undated (Box 491, Folder 1-3)
    - Television commercials: photographs, undated (Box 491, Folder 4-5)
    - Television commercial Parco Shibuya Part 2: production material, circa 1977 (Box 52)
    - Reproduction prints, undated (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Promotional material: proofs, undated (Box 597)
  - Subseries 9.15: Pierre Cardin, 1975
    - Slides and transparencies, circa 1975 (Box 416, Box 417, Box 427)
    - Posters, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Subseries 9.16: Pola XYZ, 1984-1985
    - Transparencies and photographs, circa 1984-1985 (Box 418)
    - Slides and transparencies, circa 1984-1985 (Box 450, Folder 10-11, Box 506, Folder 8-9)
    - Print ads, 1984, circa 1984 (Box 348, Folder 3-7)
    - Pola Introduces X Y Z: poster, 1985 (Box 28)
  - Subseries 9.17: Polaroid Sunglasses, undated
    - Slides, transparencies, negatives, undated (Box 427, Box 430, Folder 4, Box 450, Folder 5)
    - Poster, undated (Box 28)
  - Subseries 9.18: Renoma perfume (French Vogue), circa 1978
    - Slides, circa 1978 (Box 456, Folder 4-5)
  - Subseries 9.19: Sanyo Fashion House, 1985-1987
    Some of the I Am Very Woman ads feature Annie Leibovitz; Fiat campaign features Lisa Lyon. See Series 11 for Sanyo audiovisual material.
    - Coat: posters, 1987 (Box 29)
    - Coat: posters (oversize horizontal, four versions), 1987 (Box 311)
    - Fiat: photographs, circa 1985 (Box 174, Folder 7, Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Fiat: print ads, circa 1985 (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - Fiat: poster, 1985 (Box 29)
    - Fiat: poster (oversize horizontal), 1985 (Box 310)
    - I Am Very Woman: poster, 1986 (Box 29)
    - I Am Very Woman: posters (oversize horizontal, two versions), 1986 (Box 310)
    - I Am Very Woman (Annie Leibovitz): photographs (snapshots), circa 1986 (Box 715, Folder 26-27)
    - I Am Very Woman (Annie Leibovitz): poster, 1986 (Box 29)
    - I Am Very Woman (Annie Leibovitz): poster (oversize horizontal), 1986 (Box 310)
    - Sanyoing is Fashioning: photographs, undated (Box 194, Folder 8-10)
    - Sanyoing is Fashioning: print ads, 1985 (Box 345, Folder 6, Box 346, Folder 5-7)
    - Sanyoing is Fashioning: poster, undated (Box 29)
    - Sanyoing is Fashioning: poster (oversize horizontal), undated (Box 310)
    - Sanyoing is Fashioning: poster production material, circa 1985 (Box 346, Folder 1-3)
      Includes proofs, copy, layouts, dummies (partial), drawings, and typeface.
    - Slides, transparencies, photographs, negatives, 1980s (Box 409, Box 410, Box 411, Box 412, Box 413, Box 414, Box 415, Box 421, Folder 10)
      Binders and files boxes relating to various Sanyo campaigns. Material for I Am Very Woman (Annie Leibovitz) is in boxes 414-145.
    - Contact sheets, undated (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Television commercials: shot drawings and text, circa 1985 (Box 345, Folder 5)
    - Television commercials: storyboards (possibly Sanyo), undated (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Poster production material, undated (Box 54, Box 55)
  - Subseries 9.20: Selkon, undated
    - France Case and Space Chair: poster production material, undated (Box 56)
  - Subseries 9.21: Shiki Fabric House, 1976
    - Photographs, circa 1976 (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Transparencies, circa 1976 (Box 429)
    - Poster, 1976 (Box 30)
  - Subseries 9.22: Shiseido, 1962-1967
    Slides and transparencies contain images of posters, ads, and promotional packaging. Posters include campaigns titled Sun Oil, Sunscreen, Beauty Cake, Hair Remover, Honey Cake, Summer, and others. See Series 11 for Shiseido audiovisual material.
    - Slides and transparencies, 1966-1967, circa 1960s (Box 420, Folder 1-2, Box 428)
    - Photographs of ads, circa 1962-1967 (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper ads, 1963-1964 (Box 103)
    - Posters, circa 1962-1967 (Box 30, Box 31, Box 32)
  - Subseries 9.23: Suntory, 1976-1977
    Photographs and slides possibly relating to a campaign for the Japanese beverage company Suntory with Aurore Clement.
    - Photographs, circa 1976 (Box 204, Folder 7-8)
    - Slides and transparencies, 1976 (Box 424, Box 427)
    - Magazine ads (Fashion News), 1977 (Box 510, Folder 2-4)
  - Subseries 9.24: Tokyu, 1989
    Transparencies are mainly images of posters, but also include wrapping paper, logo. See Series 10 for examples of Tokyu wrapping paper and logo design.
    - Transparencies (binder), 1989 (Box 410, Box 431, Folder 6)
    - Advertisements, 1989 (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Poster (logo), 1989 (Box 33)
    - Posters (six designs), circa 1989 (Box 33, Box 34)
    - Poster (subway poster), circa 1989 (Box 33)
    - Poster production material (logo), undated (Box 57, Box 58)
  - Subseries 9.25: Yashica, 1970
    Advertising campaign with Toshiro Mifune for Yashica cameras. Photographs include ad photos and location snapshots.
    - Photographs and contact sheets, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 163, Folder 11-12)
    - Slides, transparencies, negatives, 1970 (Box 393, Box 426, Box 427, Box 450, Folder 7-9, Box 708)
    - Poster production material, undated (Box 59)
  - Subseries 9.26: Multiple clients, 1970s-1980s
    - Snapshots, circa 1972-1979 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Photographs (Parco and others), 1970s (Box 489, Box 490)
      Photographs of ad campaigns and projects, some marked up for publication. Includes a binder of numerous Parco campaigns (box 490).
    - Slides and transparencies, 1970s-1980s (Box 427, Box 432, Box 433)
  - Subseries 9.27: Other or unidentified campaigns, 1970s-1980s
    - Photographs, circa 1970-1979 (Box 203, Folder 17)
      Unidentified professional photographs, most likely related to advertising campaigns.
    - Photographs (snapshots) on location: various/ unidentified, circa 1970-1979 (Box 203, Folder 18, Box 715, Folder 28-33)
      Snapshots taken at unknown locations, most likely for advertising campaigns.
    - Slides and transparencies, 1970s-1980s (Box 384, Box 417, Box 432, Box 433, Box 450, Folder 12-15)
    - Give Blood Save Life: poster, undated (Box 9)
    - Japanese red blood donation campaign: slides, 1970s (Box 497)
    - Holland Casino, circa 1999 (Box 204, Folder 9)
      Snapshots of a film production from binder labeled "Holland Casino;" possibly an ad with costume work by Ishioka. See Series 11 for audiovisual material.
- Series 10: Products and packaging, 1969-1980s
  This series contains a variety of material related to packaging, products, and logotypes designed by Ishioka for a number of commercial clients. Packaging examples include a large number of cans and boxes of various sizes and colors for Maxim coffee and Yamamoto Nori seaweed. This series also includes wrapping paper designed for Tokyu, Yamagiwa, and others, as well as other products such as calendars and shopping bags. Also present is material pertaining to logotype design for several companies.
  - Subseries 10.1: Packaging, 1970s-1980s
    Some of Ishioka's packaging design for certain entities also included logotype design. See also Subseries 10.4 for material relating to packaging for Gom and Scottie.
    - Airoo chocolate: transparencies, undated (Box 496)
    - Airoo chocolate: packaging, undated (Box 330)
    - Japan Shop cigarettes: packaging, circa 1973 (Box 330)
    - Maxim coffee: design drawings, undated (Box 289)
    - Maxim coffee: photographs and transparencies (binders), circa 1987-1989 (Box 495)
    - Maxim coffee: cans and containers, undated (Box 321, Box 322, Box 323, Box 324, Box 329)
    - Maxim coffee: boxes (flat), undated (Box 338, Box 339, Box 340)
    - Maxim coffee: labels, undated (Box 598)
    - Meiji chocolate "Coffeebeat": packaging, undated (Box 329)
    - Yamamoto Nori: text and calligraphy, circa 1981 (Box 352, Folder 3)
    - Yamamoto Nori: design binder, circa 1981 (Box 428)
      Binder contains text samples and layouts, design drawings, color samples.
    - Yamamoto Nori: transparencies, circa 1981 (Box 495)
    - Yamamoto Nori: cans and boxes, 1981 (Box 325, Box 326, Box 327, Box 328, Box 329, Box 341)
    - Various: photographs of for publication, undated (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified client, undated (Box 211)
  - Subseries 10.2: Wrapping paper, 1970s-1980s
    Includes multiple examples of wrapping paper designed for several stores and companies, as well as production and related material. Some of the Yamagiwa proofs and layouts may also be related to shopping bags in Subseries 10.5.
    - Seibu, undated (Box 314)
    - Takano, undated (Box 104, Box 185, Folder 11)
    - Tokyu, circa 1989 (Box 104, Box 316, Box 317, Box 318, Box 319, Box 320)
    - Tokyu (poster versions), circa 1989 (Box 35)
    - Yamagiwa: proofs and layouts, circa 1970s (Box 106, Box 349, Folder 3, Box 350, Folder 4-7, Box 351, Folder 5-6)
    - Yamagiwa: transparencies and slides, circa 1970s (Box 495)
    - Yamagiwa catalog (with photos): production material and draft, circa 1970s (Box 350, Folder 8)
    - Yamagiwa, circa 1970s (Box 105)
    - Tokyu/Yamagiwa: preservation (Box 107)
  - Subseries 10.3: Calendars, 1969-1981
    - Parco: Dancing, 1981 (Box 187, Folder 8-9)
    - Shiseido, 1969 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Yokohama Gomu: proofs, undated (Box 108)
  - Subseries 10.4: Logotype, circa 1971-circa 1989
    Some of Ishioka's logotype work for certain entities, especially Gom and Scottie, also included packaging design. Photographs of various logos also include images of packaging. Posters for Kissa and Tokyu ad campaigns are in Series 9.
    Gom items include photographs, drawings, dummies, notes, transparencies, slides, poster, and poster production material. Scottie material includes drawings, dummies, typeface, and flat boxes.
    - Alfa Records, circa 1980 (Box 109)
    - Angle Spine Golf Stage: contact sheets and negatives, undated (Box 194, Folder 1-2)
    - Bellamica: slides and transparencies, circa 1971 (Box 495)
    - Bellamica: poster, undated (Box 2)
    - Gom (logotype and package design), circa 1975, 1979 (Box 9, Box 42, Box 204, Folder 11-12, Box 343, Box 352, Folder 6-7, Box 417, Box 496)
      Poster is in box 9; poster production material is in box 42.
    - Kissa: logo photographs, circa 1977 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Maxim, undated (Box 488, Folder 10)
    - Permanente (Issey Miyake, unrealized): drawings, typeface, undated (Box 342)
    - Scottie (logo and packaging), undated (Box 344, Box 345, Folder 1-4)
    - Tokyu (on clear plastic), circa 1989 (Box 315)
    - Various, undated (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Various: photographs, undated (Box 352, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 10.5: Other projects, 1981, undated
    Related Materials
    For other examples of shopping bags see Series 4, Subseries 4.2: Tokyo Form & Spirit.
    - Yamagiwa shopping bags, undated (Box 197)
    - Notecards: "New York Night Out Eiko", 1981 (Box 204, Folder 15)
      Includes original snapshots used in design.
  - Subseries 10.6: Portfolios: slides and transparencies (binders), 1970s-1980s (Box 496)
    Includes images of various packaging, shopping bags, calendars, logotypes, and textiles designed by Ishioka.
- Series 11: Audiovisual and born-digital material, 1965-2012
  Audiovisual material mostly relates to Ishioka's advertising work and stage projects. Material includes film, video, audio, and some commercial recordings. Record covers are in Series 8 (some have discs). This series also includes digital materials with files related to Ishioka's various design projects. These files encompass videos, photographs, font and color selections, costume sketches, graphic renderings, storyboard renderings, research material, and production notes.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS PROCESSED DIGITAL MATERIALS: Digital material will need to be viewed in the reading room on LSC's laptop. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO AUDIOVISUAL AND DIGITAL MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  Other Finding Aids
  An item-level inventory of audiovisual material is available for research use.
  - Subseries 11.1: Film, 1960s-1980s
    Film is 35mm, 16mm, and Super 8mm, and is mostly advertising, either full ads or clips, for multiple clients, especially Parco, Kadokawa Books, and Sanyo. Parco ads include Faye Dunaway campaigns (multiple ads); campaigns shot on location in India and Morocco; Don't Stare at the Nude, Be Naked; The Nightingale Sings for No One but Herself; A Model is More than Just a Pretty Face; and Kenji Sawada and Dominique Sanda campaigns. Bulk of Super 8 appears to be personal home movies, travel, and unidentified footage. Film is undated unless otherwise noted.
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    - Asahi (16mm), undated (Box 233)
    - Hitachi (16mm), undated (Box 233)
    - Jonathan Livingston Seagull (Japanese version) (35mm), undated (Box 227)
    - Kadokawa Books (35mm), 1970s (Box 216, Box 225)
    - Kadokawa Books (16mm), circa 1970s (Box 228, Box 233)
    - Kadokawa Books (Super 8mm), circa 1970s (Box 242)
    - Kanebo: An Deux Mille (16mm), circa 1979 (Box 233)
    - Nissan (16mm), circa 1971 (Box 233)
    - Parco (35mm), 1970s (Box 185, Folder 1, Box 215, Box 216, Box 221, Box 222, Box 223, Box 224, Box 225, Box 226)
    - Parco (16mm), 1970s (Box 214, Box 217, Box 218, Box 219, Box 220, Box 230, Box 231, Box 232, Box 233, Box 234)
    - Parco (Super 8mm), 1977 (Box 242)
      On location in India.
    - Parco: loose clips (bulk 35mm), circa 1970s, 1981 (Box 185, Folder 1, Box 711)
    - Sanyo (35mm), circa 1980s (Box 222)
    - Sanyo (16mm), circa 1980s (Box 233)
    - Shiseido (35mm), circa 1960s (Box 222)
    - Multiple clients (16mm) (Box 228, Box 229)
    - Issey Miyake fashion show (Super 8mm), circa 1975-1977 (Box 242)
    - Documentary about EI? (16mm), undated (Box 213)
    - Personal/unidentified (Super 8mm), circa 1970s (Box 242, Box 243)
    - Photographs separated from items 222-4 and 222-6 (Parco), circa 1970s (Box 716, Folder 31-32)
  - Subseries 11.2: Video, circa 1975-2005
    - Bram Stoker's Dracula (VHS), 1992-1993 (Box 257, Box 258)
      Includes "Academy Award Party" Vol 1 & 2, "The Making of Dracula, and "Party 4-4-93, Mr. Yagi" (possibly related).
    - "Cocoon" (Björk) (VHS) (Box 257)
    - Chushingura (S-VHS), 1997 (Box 258)
    - Epoca (D1, D2, U-matic, VHS), circa 1996 (Box 247, Box 250, Box 257)
    - Faerie Tale Theatre "Rip Van Winkle" (U-Matic), circa 1987 (Box 252)
    - The Fall (DigiBeta) (Box 250)
    - Holland Casino (U-matic), 1999 (Box 254)
    - L'Inhumaine (VHS) (Box 257)
    - Mechanisms of Density: Last Word from Paradise (HDVS or UniHI), circa 1995 (Box 250)
    - Issey Miyake: Fly With Issey and others (U-matic), circa 1975-1977 (Box 252)
    - Nike (1 inch videotape), 2005 (Box 250)
    - Parco (U-matic, VHS, Betacam), 1970s (Box 254, Box 255, Box 257)
    - Leni Riefenstahl (U-matic, Betacam, VHS), 1991, undated (Box 248, Box 251, Box 256)
    - The Ring of the Nibelung (VHS), 1999, circa 1997-1998 (Box 244)
    - Tokyo: Form & Spirit (1 inch videotape, U-matic, Video8), circa 1986 (Box 249, Box 250, Box 252, Box 265, Box 266, Box 267, Box 268, Box 269, Box 270, Box 271, Box 272, Box 273, Box 274, Box 275, Box 276, Box 277, Box 278, Box 279, Box 280, Box 281, Box 282, Box 283, Box 284)
    - Other (various formats) (Box 247, Box 250, Box 252, Box 255, Box 257, Box 258)
      Labels include: "Gallery Spoon, Scraps in NY" (1982, U-Matic, 247), "Aid & Comfort" (1987, Video8/VHS, 250/257), "Eiko by Night" (Betamax, 250), "Nippon Vogue" (Betacam/VHS, 255/257),"Pat & Eiko: Shooting in NY" (VHS, 257), "Toyota Center: Rockets Game" (VHS, 258), "Rising Sunset" (U-Matic, 252), "International Design Conference 2003" (Betacam, 255).
    - Unidentified (various formats) (Box 247, Box 248, Box 250, Box 251, Box 253, Box 254, Box 255, Box 256, Box 258)
  - Subseries 11.3: Audio, 1977-2006, undated
    Bulk appear to be recorded conversations with stakeholders of various projects. Also some answering machine recordings.
    CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    - Criss Angel, "Luxor" (microcassette), 2004-2007 (Box 235)
    - Bagunça (probably, "Brazil project") (audiocassette), undated (Box 238)
    - Bram Stoker's Dracula (microcassette), 1991, undated (Box 235)
    - Chushingura (audiocassette, microcassette), 1995-1996 (Box 235, Box 239)
    - Closet Land (audiocassette), undated (Box 241)
    - Eiko by Eiko, undated (Box 241)
    - Epoca (microcassette), 1996 (Box 235)
    - M. Butterfly (1/4 inch audiotape, audiocassette), undated (Box 250, Box 241)
    - Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters ("demo," audiocassette), undated (Box 240)
    - Issey Miyake: Fly with Issey Miyake, Issey Miyake Show (audiocassette), 1977, undated (Box 239)
    - Parco (1/4 inch audiotape, audiocassette), 1979, undated (Box 239, Box 240, Box 250)
    - Leni Riefenstahl (audiocassette), 1990, undated (Box 239)
    - Ring of Nibelung (audiocassette, microcassette), 1996-1997, undated (Box 235, Box 241)
    - The Screens (audiocassette), undated (Box 241)
    - Takemitsu: My Way of Life (audiocassette), 2003 (Box 240)
    - Other, 1985-1995, undated (Box 235, Box 236, Box 237, Box 238, Box 239, Box 240, Box 241)